Guide to the School of Visual and Performing Arts Collection RG 6.1.2
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
WCSU School of Visual and Performing Arts Collection
1850s-2008
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
Alberetti, Robert
Western Connecticut State University. School of Visual and Performing Arts
RG 6.1.2
26 Linear Feet
Pieces of art from WCSU's Art Department. Collection includes student and faculty work and gifts to the University.
Biographical / Historical
Though Western Connecticut State University has offered courses in art since early in its history, in 1950, James W. Timmons joined art faculty member Hazel D. Tobias, thereby the formation of a Department of Art was formed. In 1961, a four-year Liberal Arts (Bachelor of Arts degree) program was offered at the college and by 1967 the Art Department had five faculty members, including Robert Alberetti, with James Timmons as department. A minor in Art was offered in 1980 and in 1992, a Bachelor of Arts degree in Studio Art; painting, printmaking, or sculpture and ceramics, was made available.
During Alberetti's career at WCSU, he accumulated a collection of student art and prints which were stored in White Hall which had been the Art Department's home. Upon completion of the Art Center on the Westside campus, materials stored at White Hall were transferred to the Archives.
Arrangement
Materials are grouped in accordance with the original order of the materials as they had been stored. Prints and original pieces were collocated separately as were student works.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Scope and Contents
The collection is made up of student and faculty art as well as materials purchased by or donated to WCSU. The Collection includes: Etchings and engravings obtained from Westport antique dealer Charles Zimmerman, pieces of art collected by Professor Robert Alberetti, original art work by students and Robert Alberetti, and pieces by Allen Hermes that Alberetti had aquired. In addition, the Art Department accepted a collection of drawings (cartoons) from a local stained glass artist, Lawrence Y. Leopold. These materials were transferred to the Archives with the other materials from White Hall. Many of the stained glass drawings are in poor condition and remain lightly processed.
The pieces of art were stored in sub-optimal conditions in White Hall for many years and many sustained light damage and dirt build-up.
The collection does not contain any records from the Art department or documentation to accompany the art objects. Many of the pieces have been photographed or scanned.
When possible, pieces of original art were hung in various places in the Haas Library.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Transferred to the Archives in the summer of 2014 by Melissa Ralston-Jones and Lori Robeau for the School of Visual and Performing Arts.
Related Materials
The WCSU Miscellanea collection also includes items by James Timmons which likely belonged to the Art Department.
Engravings (prints); Watercolors (paintings).; Woodcuts; Color woodcuts; Artists' proofs.; Oil paintings.; Alberetti, Robert; Western Connecticut State University. School of Visual and Performing Arts; Leopold, Lawrence Y.; Hermes, R. Allen; Hermansader, John B., 1915–2005
- Graphic Arts Collection (AKA Print Collection), Artist and collection files
  - Correspondence and documentation, 1976-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Graphic Arts Collection Inventories, 1980-1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Graphic Arts Collection artist bios and info, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 3)
    General
    Includes information on George Karen Zhouf, Silvio Loffredo, Richard Linder, John Hermansader (collector/donor), Sigmund Abeles, Andrew Rush, Corneille, Ruth Kerkovius, Philip Kappel, Rudy Pozzatti, Leticia Tarrago, Hans Erni, Joan Silk Deckard, Edward Goerg, Raymond Gloeckler, Hedy Mannheimer, Silvio Loffredo, David Bumbeck, Paul Wunderlich, Claude Saucy, Ann Tubbs, Jim Dine, Kaethe Kollwitz, Robert Natkin, Leonel Gongora, Roland Wolff, Marcel Vertes, Jim Timmins, and George Dous.
  - Graphic Arts Collection receipts, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Connecticut Collections Exhibition Notes, Captions, etc., 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Connecticut Collection Inventories, 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Negatives, 1980s (Box 1, Folder 7)
    4 strips of negatives. Images appear to be primarily personal with some images of a painting by Riga which portrays a crown of thorns. Included also is a posed portrait of a woman who may be the artist.
- Engravings and Prints
  These items belonged to John B. Hermansader, an artist, designer and framer from West Redding, CT who is best known for his cover paintings for Jazz and Blues records in the 1940s and 50s. The original provenance of these engravings and prints is unkownn, but at least one is marked to have once belonged to East Lane Antiques of Darien, CT. Many of the items are signed by the artist and some are signed by the subject. These items were held by Robert Alberetti of the WCSU Department of Art until that departments relocation to the West Side Campus.
  - WCSU Student and Faculty Art Prints, 1980-2014 (Folder OS 1)
    General note
    OS 1: Prints by: Sheila Jones; Robert Alberetti; Susan Gracik and G. Spatola, etc (13 pieces). Includes also some original student drawings.
  - US Historic Engravings - large portraits, 1850-1950 (Folder OS 2)
    Includes: U.S. Grant (2); W.H. Harrison; David Henshaw; William B. Astor; NY Public School Society; Unidentified Woman; Samuel Sartain; General Fremont; Thadius Stevens; Schyler Colfax; Edward Everett; Ernestine Rose; Unidentified Man; Henry Clay; J.Q. Adams; Richard M. Johnson; Grover Cleveland.
  - European Historic Engravings - large portraits, 1850-1950 (Folder OS 3)
    Joseph Cotton, Esq., FRS, Deputy Master of Trinity Houser & Director of the East India Company; Turner, Charles, 1773 – 1857, (engraver); Thomas, Sir Thomas, 1769 – 1830 (artist); 1818 |The Army and The Navy; Reynolds, Samuel William, 1773 – 1835 (engraver); Knight, John Prescott, 1803 – 1881 (artist); 1839 |Interview of Charles the first with his Children; Sharp, William, 1749 – 1824 (engraver) |The Education of a Prince; Artist autograph; Eduardo Zamacois Zabala, 1841 – 1871, (artist);1870 | I.N. Madvig; Tegner, I.W., (artist)
  - Religious Themed Engravings - large portraits, 1850-1950 (Folder OS 4)
    Alonzo Potter, D.D., L.L.D.: Bishop of the PE Church of Pennsylvania; Warner, William, 1813 – 1848 (engraver); Winner, William, 1815 – 1833 (artist); 1847 | The Right Reverend Richard Channing Moore, D.D.; Maverick, Peter Rushton, 1775 – 1811 (engraver); Dunlap, William, 1766 – 1839 (artist); 1823 | Rev. James Milnor D.D.; Page, William, (engraver); Ingham, Charles, (artist) | Clergymen of New York and Brooklyn; Ritter, Nathan (publisher); 1885 | Giuramento di Leon III (The Oath of Leo III); Garelli, Luigi (engraver); Raffaele Sanzio (original artist); Late 19th century | Le Tre Virtu (The Three Virtues); Ortis, Niccola (engraver); Raffaele Sanzio (original artist); Late 19th century | Fides Salvam Fecit (The Faith has Healed); Gozzini, Vincenzo c. 1790 (engraver); Dolci, Carlo 1616 – 1686 (original artist); 1823
  - Small U.S. Colonial Engraved Portraits, 1850-1950 (Folder small 5)
    James Duane (1733 – 1797) | Benedict Arnold (1741 – 1801)
  - Small U.S. 19th Century Engraved Portraits, 1850-1950 (Folder small 6)
    Philip William Otterbein (1726 – 1813) | David Millard (1794 – 1873) | William H. Seward (1801 – 1872) | Aaron Ogden (1756 – 1839)| Lewis Cass (1782 – 1866) | Richard Penn Smith (1799 – 1854) | Thomas Hart Benton (1782 – 1858) | John Jacob Astor (1763 – 1848) | Amos Lawrence (1786 – 1852)
  - Small European Engraved Portraits, 1850-1950 (Folder small 7)
    Prince Albert of Saxe-Coburg and Gotha (1819 – 1861) | John Calvin (1509 – 1564) | Martin Luther (1483 – 1546) | Sir Francis Walsingham (1532 – 1590) |Thomas Howard (1536 – 1572) | Lady Arabella Stuart (1575 – 1615)
  - Miscellaneous Art Images, 1850-1950 (Folder OS 8)
    10 items, still-lifes, dogs, etc.
  - Miscellaneous Images, 1850-1950 (Folder OS 9)
    Unidentified portraits and scenes, mostly engravings; includes very old clippings pasted on boards
- Stained Glass by Lawrence Ysbrand Leopold (1934-2014)
  Biographical / Historical
  Lawrence Ysbrand Leopold (1934-2014) was born and grew up on a farm in Pennsylvania where his father made leaded glass. Taking his artistic skill with his familial experience with leaded glass, the younger Leopold apprenticed in a stained glass shop in Florida in the 1950s until his boss encouraged him to move to Germany to learn from a master craftsman. For three years Leopold served an apprenticeship in Munich, Germany. In 1958, Leopold returned to this country and eventually opened a shop in New York City. In the late 1970s he moved to Connecticut. The New Haven Register (CT) - Sunday, May 28, 1989 wrote of Leopold: "Leopold is a master craftsman whose stained glass windows can be seen in churches and temples around the world. His work can be found in Germany, where he learned his skills as an apprentice, and in Vietnam, where he created a stained glass window for a memorial chapel. It can also be found in Mexico, South America, throughout the United States and in parts of Canada. Tucked away in the basement of the general store in Pleasant Valley, near the town of Barkhamsted, Leopold creates magic with colored glass, paint, a variety of hand tools, lead, a kiln and a bounty of God-given talent."
  To create a piece of stained glass, the artist makes a sketch; once the sketch is approved or is acceptable, a cartoon, or pattern, is made on heavy paper the actual size as the window. The pattern is then cut and used to cut with special cutting wheels the colored glass that will be used in the window. Each piece is painted with a special paint and are fired in a kiln to permanently embed the paint into the glass. The pieces are assembled with flexible lead fitted around the edges of the glass pieces.
  This collection includes sketches and cartoons for stained glass. The pieces were commissioned by churches, private schools, and private residences. Church designs are Roman Catholic, Eastern Orthodox, and Protestant. Among those; Mt. Zion, A.M.E., Danbury, CT; Trinity Episcopal, Torrington, CT; Advent Christian, Torrington, CT Immanuel Lutheran, Bristol, CT; St. Stephens Episcopal, Delmar, NY; The Church of St. Patrick, Farmington, CT; and the Chapel at Kent School, Kent, CT. Leopold is credited on many of the designs and layouts.
  - Nativity Scene, undated (Tube 1, Item 1)
  - Resurrection, undated (Tube 1, Item 2)
    Multiple parts; Lakeland, FL
  - [Christ Revealed], undated (Tube 1, Item 3)
  - Good Shepherd, undated (Tube 1, Item 4)
  - Ascension, undated (Tube 1, Item 5)
  - Saints Symbols, undated (Tube 1, Item 6)
    Multiple parts
  - Baptism, undated (Tube 1, Item 7)
    Lakeland, FL
  - The Conversion of St. Paul, undated (Tube 1, Item 8)
  - Resurrection, undated (Tube 1, Item 9)
  - Church Triumphant, undated (Tube 1, Item 10)
  - Baptism, undated (Tube 1, Item 11)
  - Knocking at the Door, undated (Tube 1, Item 12)
  - St. Peter and St. Paul, undated (Tube 1, Item 13)
  - Pentecost, undated (Tube 1, Item 14)
  - Hochzeit, undated (Tube 1, Item 15)
  - Walking on Water, undated (Tube 1, Item 16)
  - Christ in Temple, undated (Tube 1, Item 17)
  - Hochzeil von Canaan, undated (Tube 1, Item 18)
  - St. Bartholomew, undated (Tube 2, Item 19)
  - Leper & Christ Healing Leper with Saints, undated (Tube 2, Item 20)
  - Prodigal Son, undated (Tube 2, Item 21)
  - Good Shepherd, undated (Tube 2, Item 22)
  - Sower - Reapers, undated (Tube 2, Item 23)
  - Christ with Children, undated (Tube 2, Item 24)
    Mt. Zion, A.M.E., Danbury, CT
  - Francis Ashbury, undated (Tube 2, Item 25)
  - Hospital Window, undated (Tube 2, Item 26)
  - Knocking at the Door, undated (Tube 2, Item 27)
    Waterbury
  - Sower, undated (Tube 2, Item 28)
  - Untitled, undated (Tube 2, Item 29)
  - Good Shepherd, undated (Tube 2, Item 30)
    Elizabeth Brown, Thomaston, CT
  - Bear, undated (Tube 2, Item 31)
    Multiple parts; Riverton
  - Baptism, undated (Tube 2, Item 32)
  - Last Supper, undated (Tube 2, Item 33)
  - God the Father, undated (Tube 2, Item 34)
  - Good Sheppard, undated (Tube 2, Item 35)
  - Angels, undated (Tube 2, Item 36)
    Lawrence Y. Leopold
  - Olberg (no Christ figure), undated (Tube 2, Item 37)
  - bust, Blessed Virgin Mary, undated (Tube 2, Item 38)
  - Saints / Pentecost, undated (Tube 3, Item 39)
  - Mary / Child, undated (Tube 3, Item 40)
    Cold Spring
  - Wisemen, undated (Tube 3, Item 41)
    Camden S.C.
  - St. Peter, undated (Tube 3, Item 42)
  - Prodigal Son x3, undated (Tube 3, Item 43)
  - Olberg, undated (Tube 3, Item 44)
  - Crucifixion, undated (Tube 3, Item 45)
    Plainville CT
  - Prodigal Son, undated (Tube 3, Item 46)
    (La Grande) Left hand light, Trinity Window
  - Sheppard's, undated (Tube 3, Item 47)
    Camden SC
  - Annunciation, undated (Tube 3, Item 48)
  - Priest with communion, undated (Tube 3, Item 49)
  - Feeding the 5,000, undated (Tube 3, Item 50)
    Multiple parts; Oswego NY
  - Be fishers of Men, undated (Tube 3, Item 51)
    Canaan CT
  - Born of the spirit / Laying of Hands, undated (Tube 3, Item 52)
  - St. Paul, undated (Tube 3, Item 53)
  - Finding in the Temple, undated (Tube 3, Item 54)
  - Sacred Heart of Jesus, undated (Tube 3, Item 55)
  - Christ with kids, undated (Tube 3, Item 56)
  - St. Andrew, undated (Tube 3, Item 57)
    Multiple parts; Kent CT
  - Untitled, undated (Tube 3, Item 58)
  - Isaiah, undated (Tube 3, Item 59)
  - Christ teaching /Last Supper, ca.1950-1960 (Tube 4, Item 60)
    Branford CT
  - Simon Peter, undated (Tube 4, Item 61)
    Episcopal Church,Torrington CT
  - Walking on Water / Calming the Tempest, undated (Tube 4, Item 62)
  - Blessed Virgin Mary with Child, undated (Tube 4, Item 63)
  - Angels, undated (Tube 4, Item 64)
  - Mary with Child, undated (Tube 4, Item 65)
  - Christ with Child, undated (Tube 4, Item 66)
  - St. Peter, undated (Tube 4, Item 67)
  - Laying on of Hands, undated (Tube 4, Item 68)
    Long Hill CT [Trumbull]
  - Nativity, undated (Tube 4, Item 69)
  - Angel with Harp, undated (Tube 4, Item 70)
  - Untitled, undated (Tube 4, Item 71)
    Immanuel Lutheran, Bristol CT
  - Bust of Bishop, undated (Tube 4, Item 72)
  - Our Lady of Lavallette, undated (Tube 4, Item 73)
  - Untitled, undated (Tube 4, Item 74)
  - Untitled, undated (Tube 4, Item 75)
  - Untitled, undated (Tube 4, Item 76)
  - Ascension, undated (Tube 4, Item 77)
    Multiple parts; Long Hill CT [Trumbull]
  - Christ on the Cross, undated (Tube 5, Item 78)
  - [Christ with children], undated (Tube 5, Item 79)
  - Gethsemane, undated (Tube 5, Item 80)
  - St. Peter, undated (Tube 5, Item 81)
  - Lazarus, undated (Tube 5, Item 82)
  - Ten lepers, undated (Tube 5, Item 83)
  - Holy Spirit, undated (Tube 5, Item 84)
    Multiple parts; St. Stephen, Delmar [NY?]
  - Prodigal Son, undated (Tube 5, Item 85)
  - [Archangel Michael], undated (Tube 5, Item 86)
  - [Miscellaneous musical instruments], undated (Tube 5, Item 87)
    St. Luke's
  - Child of Prague, undated (Tube 5, Item 88)
    Eastern Orthodox
  - Beehive, undated (Tube 5, Item 89)
  - Justice, undated (Tube 5, Item 90)
  - [Wright window], undated (Tube 5, Item 91)
    Pawling, NY - Harold S. (Starr) Wright, Gertrude S. (Stuart) Wright
  - Palm Sunday, undated (Tube 5, Item 92)
  - Eucharist, undated (Tube 5, Item 93)
    Tampa
  - St. Matthew, undated (Tube 5, Item 94)
  - Ship United, undated (Tube 5, Item 95)
  - Christ with Lamb, undated (Tube 5, Item 96)
  - Christ in the Temple, undated (Tube 5, Item 97)
    Chicopee, Mass.
  - Christ / children, undated (Tube 5, Item 98)
  - [Coat of] Arms / Shapes, undated (Tube 5, Item 99)
  - Walking on Water, 2006 (Tube 5, Item 100)
    Multiple parts; Advent Church, Torrington, CT
  - Christ with Children, undated (Tube 6, Item 101)
    In Memory of John and Hazel Cowell; Advent Church, Torrington, CT
  - [Flowers], undated (Tube 6, Item 102)
  - Fred's Roses, undated (Tube 6, Item 103)
  - Untitled, undated (Tube 6, Item 104)
    David Livingston; Laconia, NH (Private Home)
  - His Only Son, undated (Tube 6, Item 105)
    Torrington, CT
  - Pegasus, undated (Tube 6, Item 106)
  - Hunt (20's Figures), undated (Tube 6, Item 107)
  - Untitled, undated (Tube 6, Item 108)
  - Several Mc. Panels, 2004 (Tube 6, Item 109)
  - Jesus Praying, undated (Tube 6, Item 110)
    In Memory of Barbara Allen Connell; Advent Church, Torrington, CT
  - 2 Johns + Ark, 2004 (Tube 6, Item 111)
    Multiple parts; St John's, Sandwich, MA
  - Baptism of Christ, undated (Tube 6, Item 112)
  - Old Saybrook, undated (Tube 6, Item 113)
  - Christ with Children, undated (Tube 6, Item 114)
  - Music, undated (Tube 6, Item 115)
  - Dog in Profile, undated (Tube 6, Item 116)
  - Untitled, undated (Tube 6, Item 117)
    Multiple parts; Home of Dennis Peter
  - Flowers and Trees, undated (Tube 6, Item 118)
  - St. Paul, undated (Tube 6, Item 119)
    Multiple parts; Delmar
  - Seeded Glass, 2004 (Tube 6, Item 120)
  - Paul, undated (Tube 6, Item 121)
  - Butterfly, undated (Tube 6, Item 122)
  - Ship, undated (Tube 6, Item 123)
    Multiple parts; L. Ysbrand Leopold
  - Tom's Panel, 2005 (Tube 6, Item 124)
  - Dan's Bath Panel, 2003 (Tube 6, Item 125)
  - St. Frances de Chantal / Symbols, undated (Tube 6, Item 126)
  - Miracle in Canaan, undated (Tube 6, Item 127)
  - US Armed Forces Symbol, undated (Tube 6, Item 128)
  - Americana, Etc., undated (Tube 7, Item 129)
  - Mother and Daughter at Stream, undated (Tube 7, Item 130)
  - Jesus at Gethsemane w/ Angel, undated (Tube 7, Item 131)
  - Simple Floral, undated (Tube 7, Item 132)
  - Fruit and Vegetables, undated (Tube 7, Item 133)
  - Rose, undated (Tube 7, Item 134)
  - Christ with Children, undated (Tube 7, Item 135)
    Christ Church, Manchester, NH
  - Bear II, undated (Tube 7, Item 136)
  - Roses, undated (Tube 7, Item 137)
  - Music Canopy, undated (Tube 7, Item 138)
    St. Pat's, Farmington, CT
  - Thomas Cromwell, undated (Tube 7, Item 139)
  - Tower, 2000 (Tube 7, Item 140)
    Multiple parts; Wallingford, CT
  - House Job - Paul, undated (Tube 7, Item 141)
  - Cup/Grapes/Wine, undated (Tube 7, Item 142)
  - Baptism, undated (Tube 7, Item 143)
  - Baptism, undated (Tube 7, Item 144)
  - Lisa's Panel, undated (Tube 7, Item 145)
  - Eagle's, undated (Tube 7, Item 146)
  - Tom's Dogwood, undated (Tube 7, Item 147)
  - Madonna and Child, undated (Tube 7, Item 148)
  - Road to Emmaus, undated (Tube 7, Item 149)
  - Good Shepherd, undated (Tube 7, Item 150)
  - Christ with 2 Children, 1936 (Tube 7, Item 151)
    California
  - Wisteria, undated (Tube 7, Item 152)
  - Hochzeit (Wedding in Canaan), undated (Tube 7, Item 153)
  - Tom's Panel's, undated (Tube 7, Item 154)
  - George Washington Praying, undated (Tube 7, Item 155)
  - Old Farms School, undated (Tube 7, Item 156)
  - Kent School - Chapel, 1932-2001 (Tube 7, Item 157)
    Multiple parts; Kent, CT, Contains panel designs, crests, graduate donor names - attributed to L. Ysbrand Leopold
  - Kent School - Chapel, 1996 (Tube 7, Item 157.1)
    Multiple parts; Kent, CT, Coat of Arms design, graduate donor names- attributed to L. Ysbrand Leopold
  - Lazarus, undated (Tube 8, Item 158)
  - Christ, undated (Tube 8, Item 159)
    Top portion is torn off and missing
  - The Good Shepherd, undated (Tube 8, Item 160)
  - Crucifixion with Longinus, undated (Tube 8, Item 161)
  - Knocking at the Door, undated (Tube 8, Item 162)
  - Tablets, undated (Tube 8, Item 163)
  - Palm Sunday, undated (Tube 8, Item 164)
  - Pentecost, undated (Tube 8, Item 165)
  - Music with Angels, undated (Tube 8, Item 166)
  - Christ Ascension, undated (Tube 8, Item 167)
  - Abraham and Isaac, undated (Tube 8, Item 168)
  - Miscellaneous scraps and torn pieces, undated (Tube 9, Item 169)
- Student Art
  - Unknown; Nude with Sunflower, undated; 33.75 x 61; oil on canvas (Item 33)
    Filename: DSCF0278
  - Bartlet, Jessica; Icy Rock II, undated; 6.75 x 5.5; oil on panel (Item 96)
    Filename: DSCF0353
  - Davidson, Betsy; Clump, undated; 13 x 16.50; oil on panel (Item 97)
    Filename: DSCF0354
  - Gambinelli, Jim; The Old Caddy, undated; 9 x 12; Acrylic on Masonite (Item 98)
    Filename: DSCF0355
  - Bartone, Karen; The Embrace, undated; 22 x 22 x 22; oil on panel (Item 99)
    Filename: DSCF0322
  - Rossi, Renee; Search for Stability, undated; 19.75 x 19.75; oil on paper (Item 100)
    Filename: DSCF0323
  - Obee, Perry; Self Portrait with Postcards, undated; 37 x 30; oil on paper/foam core (Item 101)
    Filename: DSCF0325
  - Dunn, Kevin; Still Life of a Pallete, undated; 30 x 30; oil on canvas (Item 102)
    Filename: DSCF0326
  - Bowers, Tracy; Toolshed Treasures, undated; 24 x 36; oil on canvas (Item 105)
    Filename: DSCF0330
  - Tavolacci, Eileen; Untitled, undated; 14 x 18; oil on canvas (Item 106)
    Filename: DSCF0332
  - McDonald, Brie; Birds, undated; 16 x 15.25; oil on panel (Item 107)
    Filename: DSCF0333
  - Day, Isabele; In the Studio, undated; 16 x 14; oil on canvas (Item 108)
    Filename: DSCF0336
  - Stewart-Wright, Sarah; Grey Abstract, undated; 48 x 48; oil on canvas (Item 109)
    Filename: DSCF0338
  - Gonzales, Mat; Extrateresterals, undated; 25.50 x 19.75; Print (Item 93)
    Filename: DSCF0321
  - Unknown; Photograph of a man with gas mask, undated; 14.25 x 18.25; Print (Item 94)
    Filename: DSCF0351
  - D'Andrea, Emily; Digital Still Life, undated; 12.25 x 16.25; Print (Item 95)
    Filename: DSCF0352
  - Unknown; Composite graphic art portrait I, undated; 30 x 40; Print (Item 103)
    Filename: DSCF0327
  - Unknown; Composite graphic art portrait II, undated; 30 x 40; Print (Item 104)
    Filename: DSCF0329
  - Megan Marden painting, untitled, 2008; 42 x 50", mixed media on canvas (Item 113)
  - Prunty, ?; Acceptance, undated; 24x36", framed print (Box 113.1)
  - Unknown; [Card Players], undated; 22x30",matted print (Folder OS 1.1, Item 114)
  - Unknown; [Escapism], undated; 32x42", poster on foam core (Folder OS 1.1, Item 115)
  - Smouynde, Ewa?; [Bedroom], undated; 8x10", print (two copies) (Folder OS 1.1, Item 116)
  - Lee, Shawna; After the Ride, 1994; 22x32", print (Folder OS 1.1, Item 117)
  - Gerhardt, ?; [1500s Sailing Ship], 1969; 9x11", print (Folder OS 1.1, Item 118)
  - Mathis, Cynthia; [Smiling Guy], undated; 12 x 24", print (Folder OS 1.1, Item 119)
  - Maiz, Aline; The Stair Master, undated; 8x10", print (Folder OS 1.1, Item 121)
  - Unknown; Gateway in the Sands, undated; 6x10", matted print (Folder OS 1.1, Item 121)
  - Meyer, Nathan; [Jazz Band], undated; 10"x10" (Folder OS 1.1, Item 122)
  - Unknown; [Welded Iron Abstract Bust], undated (Item 123)
    30 x 36", Iron sculpture
  - [Untitled Abstract, white with black and brown lines], undated (Item 124)
    70 x 60", oil on canvas
- Miscellaneous Original Art
  - Zhouf, Georges; The Passion, undated; 40.5 x 29.5; painting (Item 2)
    Barcode: 7803W03688 | Filename: DSCF0217
  - Lindher, Richard; 1st Ave., undated; 27.5 x 33.5; painting (Item 10)
    Barcode: 7803W03610 | Filename: DSCF0232
  - Davies, Archer B.; Men in Agony, undated; 24 x 21; charocoal (Box OS 1, Item 19)
    Barcode: 7803W03617 | Filename: DSCF0256
  - Nigat, (?); Abstract black and purple, undated; 29.75 x 30.75; oil on canvas (Item 29)
    Filename: DSCF0274
  - Unknown; Abstract in White Frame, undated; 26 x 19.5; paper print or water color (Item 30)
    Filename: DSCF0275
  - Tubbs, Ann M.; Cow Dreams, undated; 23.5 x 48.25; Mixed Media (Item 41)
    Barcode: 7803W03663 | Filename: DSCF0293
  - Giacometti, Alberto; Nude, undated; 14.75 x 10.75; Charcoal (Item 50)